mercuryinsurance.com 2017-01-31

# Mercury Insurance | Policy Statement

Mercury and its affiliated companies appreciate the trust you place in us when you ask us to help protect you and your assets. You trust us with your private, personal information when you purchase insurance from us, and we are committed to protecting this information. Mercury does not sell information about you to others.

### Mercury's Use of Your Personal Information

We treat your information with respect and concern for your privacy. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted or required by law.

For example, we may share any or all of your information with our affiliated companies. We may also disclose any or all information we have collected about you to companies that perform services on our behalf.

When we make this type of disclosure it is done to service your Mercury account or policy, or to inform you about Mercury products and services. Before disclosing your information, we require these companies to agree to keep it confidential and use it only for the transaction we request.

### Independent Mercury Agents

The independent insurance agents authorized to sell Mercury products and services are not Mercury employees, but they are subject to Mercury's Privacy Policy, to the extent that they sell or service our products, unless they have provided you with a copy of their own privacy policy. Because they have a unique business relationship with you, they may have additional personal information about you that Mercury does not. They may use this information differently than Mercury. Contact your Mercury Agent or advisor to learn more about their privacy practices.

## Information About Mercury's Websites

### Information collected

Mercury collects personal information (for example, name, address, E-mail address, telephone number or Social Security number) on our web site only when you voluntarily provide it to us. We do not collect any personally identifiable information about your online activities across other sites or online services. Only your Internet domain is recognized when you visit our website; your individual E-mail address is not.

If you provide us with your E-mail address, Mercury may use it to occasionally notify you of new services, special offers, or to confirm transactions. If you do not wish to be contacted by E-mail you may click on the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any Mercury E-mail you receive and you will no longer receive non-policy related communications from us via E-mail.

The companies of Mercury Insurance Group may work with several third-party vendors, including, but not necessarily limited to [Yahoo!/Bing](https://www.bing.com/), [Google](https://www.google.com/), [AdHarmonics](http://www.adharmonics.com/), [Rocket Fuel](https://rocketfuel.com/), [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/), [YouTube](https://www.youtube.com/), [Sizmek](https://www.sizmek.com/), [Oracle BlueKai](https://www.oracle.com/marketingcloud/products/data-management-platform/index.html) and others, to research usage and activities on our website. These third-party vendors use Web beacons and cookies to conduct this research. The information collected through these Web beacons and cookies is used to find out more about our Web site usage patterns, for more accurate reporting, and to improve the effectiveness of our marketing. These vendors may collect information about the online activity of visitors to our website for the purpose of customizing ads to your interests (sometimes referred to as "interest-based" advertising). No personally identifiable information is collected. Information recorded through the use of these Web beacons and cookies is aggregated and then shared with us. No personally identifiable information about you is shared by these third-party vendors with the Mercury family of companies. 

To opt out of interest-based advertising, please visit the following websites:

Digital Advertising Alliance  
<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

Networking Advertising Initiative  
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

Oracle Data Cloud  
<http://bluekai.com/consumers.php>

###### _To learn more about how Mercury collects and uses your personal information, please read the following notice._

### Mercury's Sources of Information About You

We may collect personal information about you from:

  * The information you provide on quotes, applications or other forms (such as your name, address and Social Security number)
  * Your transactions with us (such as your payment history and claims information)
  * The information we receive from a consumer reporting agency (such as your credit history, your driving record, and claims history with other insurance carriers)
  * Your insurance agent/broker (such as updated information pertaining to your account)
  * Public records (such as motor vehicle reports and criminal records)

### Information sharing and use

Mercury does not sell information about you to others. If you only browse our website and do not supply any information, you will not receive unsolicited E-mail, telephone calls, or other marketing materials from Mercury as a result of your visit.

When you make changes to your account or request more information about our products we may forward information you supply to us to your Mercury Independent Insurance Agent. We do this so they can service your account or contact you with additional information about our products.

### Cookies

**Mercury uses cookies to maintain the continuity of browser sessions and to track repeat visitors. No personally identifiable information about you is stored in these cookies.**

### Browsers & Security

Mercury uses **secure technology, which encrypts** information as it crosses the Internet. You can tell if you are visiting a secure area by looking at the padlock symbol on your browser screen. If it is "locked," you have a secure session.

Mercury has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of your personal information. Our servers are located in the United States of America and are designed to prevent unauthorized access.

### Links to other sites

MercuryInsurance.com contains links to other websites. These other websites are not under Mercury's direct control, and they may collect information about you that Mercury does not. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of linked websites.

### Protecting Your Personal Information from Unauthorized Access

We limit employee access to customer information to those employees with a legitimate business reason for such access. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information from being accessed by unauthorized persons. We also conduct regular risk assessment, risk management and control, and oversight of our service providers to assure the effectiveness of these safeguards.

### Your Medical Information

Mercury obtains medical information only in connection with specific products or claims. We will not use or share personally identifiable medical information for any purpose other than the underwriting or administration of your policy, claim or account, or as otherwise disclosed to you when the information is collected.

### Reviewing Your Information

If you submitted information to Mercury online and would like to review that information, please request a copy of the information about you that we have in our files to review it for completeness and accuracy. Your request must be in writing. Please contact your Agent to submit your request.

## Changes to this Statement

The effective date of this Statement was July 1, 2004. Please be aware that we may periodically update or revise this Statement, and any changes are effective as of the date posted. Please check our Consumer Privacy Statement frequently for changes.

### This Privacy Statement applies to the following members of the Mercury Family of Companies:

##### Arizona

Mercury Casualty Company

##### California

Mercury Insurance Company  
Mercury Casualty Company  
American Mercury Insurance Company  
California Automobile Insurance Company  
Auto Insurance Specialists, LLC

##### Florida

Mercury Insurance Company of Florida  
Mercury Casualty Company  
American Mercury Insurance Company

##### Georgia

Mercury Insurance Company of Georgia  
Mercury Indemnity Company of Georgia  
American Mercury Insurance Company

##### Illinois

Mercury Insurance Company of Illinois  
Mercury National Insurance Company

##### Michigan

Mercury National Insurance Company

##### Nevada

Mercury Casualty Company

##### New Jersey

Mercury Indemnity Company of America  
Mercury Insurance Company of Illinois

##### New York

Mercury Casualty Company

##### Oklahoma

American Mercury Insurance Company

##### Pennsylvania

Mercury Insurance Company of Florida  
Mercury Insurance Company of Illinois

##### Texas

Mercury County Mutual Insurance Company  
American Mercury Insurance Company  
American Mercury Lloyds Insurance Company

##### Virginia

Mercury Casualty Company  
American Mercury Insurance Company

##### Mercury Select Management Company, Inc.

All states with the exception of Connecticut and Maine.

##### PoliSeek AIS Insurance Solutions, Inc.
